// src/components/data.js
const data = [
  {
    question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
    option1: "Modem",
    option2: "Router",
    option3: "LAN Cable",
    option4: "Pen Drive",
    ans: "Modem",
  },
  {
    question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
    option1: "Asia",
    option2: "Europe",
    option3: "North America",
    option4: "Africa",
    ans: "Africa",
  },
  {
    question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
    option1: "Spam",
    option2: "Fake",
    option3: "Archived",
    option4: "Bin",
    ans: "Spam",
  },
  {
    question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
    option1: "Application Software",
    option2: "Internet",
    option3: "Operating System",
    option4: "Mouse",
    ans: "Operating System",
  },
  {
    question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
    option1: "Index Page",
    option2: "Homepage",
    option3: "Sitemap",
    option4: "Pen Drive",
    ans: "Homepage",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the command to create a new React application?",
    option1: "npx create-react-app my-app",
    option2: "npm install react",
    option3: "create-react-app my-app",
    option4: "npm start",
    ans: "npx create-react-app my-app",
  },
  {
    question: "Which method is used to update state in a React component?",
    option1: "updateState",
    option2: "setState",
    option3: "changeState",
    option4: "modifyState",
    ans: "setState",
  },
  {
    question: "Which hook is used to manage state in a functional component?",
    option1: "useEffect",
    option2: "useContext",
    option3: "useReducer",
    option4: "useState",
    ans: "useState",
  },
  {
    question: "What is JSX?",
    option1: "A syntax extension for JavaScript",
    option2: "A type of component",
    option3: "A CSS preprocessor",
    option4: "A state management tool",
    ans: "A syntax extension for JavaScript",
  },
  {
    question: "Which lifecycle method is called after a component is rendered for the first time?",
    option1: "componentDidMount",
    option2: "componentWillUnmount",
    option3: "componentDidUpdate",
    option4: "componentWillMount",
    ans: "componentDidMount",
  },
];

export default data;
